PAOLO CARCAMO JUNIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- paolo.n.carcamo@gmail.com
- **** 778-979-6858
- **♀** Vancouver, BC
- in /in/paolo-carcamo/
- paolocarcamo

I am a previous Hospitality Professional with an array of Managerial experience within the expertise of Food & Beverage Operations and Events. Always striving for nothing less than genuine excellence in every relationship and every opportunity. Exhilarated to have been introduced to the possibilities of Tech through the London App **Brewery Web** Development Bootcamp. With the orchestration of back-end and front-end technologies, I am drawn to the endless possibilities of creating impactful and aesthetically elegant solutions that could

> Skills

potentially change the

world, including my own.

Javascript
HTML5
CSS3
React
Node.js
Express
MongoDB
Github

> Education

Florida State University Bachelor of Science in Hospitality Administration & Management 2013

The App Brewery
Udemy - Web Development Certification 2020

Employment

JW Marriott Parq Vancouver

Vancouver, BC Sept. 2019 to Current

Associate Event Manager

Manages up to 15 groups per month within a dual-property hotel with 500+ rooms and 67,000+ sq. ft. of convention space

- · Initializes pre-planning with clients in order to develop detailed event orders and custom floor plans.
- Prepares and analyzes billing documents for every group.
- Reports out on catering and room projections with an average 4% error margin.
- · Coordinates interdepartmental cooperation in order to deliver an exceptional experience for every group.

Vancouver, BC Aug. 2018 to Sept. 2019

Event Coorinator

- Supported Event Managers throughout all areas of Planning, Administration, and Execution of multi-day programs ranging from THTB Groups to multi-day Conferences of up to 1,200 attendees.
- · Curated Sales Contracts to be sent to Turnover for Event Managers to start detailing.
- Utilized the co-operation and relationships of all Departments within the hotel to execute the best possible product and service for our guests.
- Familiar with programs such as CI-TY, Opera, Hotshop, Social Tables, Meeting Matrix, and Micros.

Vancouver, BC Dec. 2017 to Aug. 2018

Banquet & Food Services Manager

- Managed and developed a department alongside 3 co-managers, 4 captains, 2 event concierge, and 90+ staff members.
- Managed day-to-day operations within 67,000+ sq. ft. of convention space and the operation of the hotel's In-Room Dining and Executive Club Lounge.
- Managed weekly scheduling for the Banquet Department.
- Developed relationships with clients to increase likelihood of their return and ensure a successful program.

Walt Disney World Swan and Dolphin

Orlando, FL Apr. 2016 to Dec. 2017

Assistant Banquet Manager

- Managed a Department with a team of 3 co-managers, 8 captains, and 400+ staff members that consistently executed functions equating to \$45 million in annual revenue.
- Supported the Event Management Team to deliver exceptional service resulting in ESS scores amounting to Swan: #1 & Dolphin: #4 on overall "intent to recommend" amongst our competitive set.
- Oversaw day-to-day operations within 350,000+ sq. ft. of convention space.
- Managed programs with more than 50-100 suites in support of In-Room Dining.
- Effectively built relationships with 9 Catering Managers to execute extraordinary and successful programs with all of our clients.

> Projects

Digital CV

- A simple, but elegant digital CV to showcase my skills and ambitions.
- Made with pure HTML and CSS
- Live Demo: https://paolocarcamo.github.io/digital_cv/

Tindog Landing Page

- A mock product page for the "Tindog" application based on a spoof of Tinder.
- Made with HTML and CSS with a focus on practicing CSS Styling. Use of Bootstrap framework.
- Live Demo: https://paolocarcamo.github.io/tindog-landing-page/

Chat App Challenge

- Frontend Mentor Challenge to create this mock landing page for a chat app advertisement.
- Made with pure HTML and CSS
- Live Demo: https://paolocarcamo.github.io/css-chat-app-challenge/

GitFinder

- · Github User Search App where users can search for other users within the Github Community.
- Made with React.js and the Github Public API. Use of Functional Components, useContext, and useReducer Hooks.
- Live Demo: https://qitfinder38242.netlify.app/

Panda Erica Website (Under Construction)

- A collaborative personal project to build a custom website for a children's book designer & illustrator.
- Made with React.js
- Live Demo | `Preliminary Designs`: https://github.com/paolocarcamo/panda-erica-website